<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on DataOps</title>
    <link>http://dataops.info/portfolio/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on DataOps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2017 Locke Data Ltd</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 18:25:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://dataops.info/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>DataOps Summit</title>
      <link>http://dataops.info/portfolio/DataOpsSummit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dataops.info/portfolio/DataOpsSummit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DataOps Summit is an annual conference &amp;amp; exhibition series focused on the technologies, tools and best practices for operationalizing data products at scale. This year’s DataOps Summit 2017 is being held on June 20 – 21, 2017 at The Westin Boston Waterfront and Boston Convention Center. Located in the thriving Seaport district, the conference venue is conveniently located in Boston’s vibrant innovation district, home to high-tech firms and leading academic institutions. The Summit is set to attract data professionals and business executives from around the world. Exposure to in-depth training, exceptional speakers, and powerful networking opportunities are key benefits of attending DataOps Summit 2017.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>arapaima.uk</title>
      <link>http://dataops.info/portfolio/Arapaima/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dataops.info/portfolio/Arapaima/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Gavin Campbell, a freelance database developer specialised in improving working practices in database delivery through the use of tools such as SQL Server Data Tools, tSQLt, Visual Studio Team Services, Git and Jenkins, on platforms such as AWS and Microsoft Azure, and methodologies such as Continuous Delivery and Agile.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locke Data</title>
      <link>http://dataops.info/portfolio/LockeData/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dataops.info/portfolio/LockeData/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Locke Data is a Data Science consultancy aimed at helping companies get started with data science the right way. Focussing on building internal skills and sensible processes, Locke Data starts implementing DataOps in organisations from day 1.
&lt;iframe width=&#34;560&#34; height=&#34;315&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/64PIa9gcuh0&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Snow Labs</title>
      <link>http://dataops.info/portfolio/JohnSnowLabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dataops.info/portfolio/JohnSnowLabs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;John Snow Labs specialise in providing turnkey data solutions that save months of data gathering and cleaning.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>